

MY BACKGROUND

Highly driven Frontend Developer professional with 3+ years of development experience. Inquisitive and proactive in learning about the latest technology to help improve and enhance the company and team productivity. Fast learner with a positive attitude and willing to take up new challenges. Result driven, focus on efficiency and creativity in development and problem solving.

PROJECT APPS

- MyBaiki (Product Management Solution)
- MyAestic (Healtcare services)
- Getudio (Booking Facilities)
- Altica E-Commerce (WordPress)

SKILLS

- Wordpress E-commerce
- HTML5
- PHP
- JavaScript
- Wordpress E-commerce
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe XD / FIGMA
- Ionic Framework
- Flowchart (Lucidchart)

PROFESSIONAL

- Communication skills
- Ability to solve problem
- Able to work as team well as an individual
- Good at time management

LANGUAGES

- Spoken and written
- Malay (Expert)
- English (Intermediate)

CONTACT



+[60] 123024855



huzairulshazmey00@gmail.com



<u>huzairulshazmey</u>



github.com/huzairulshazmey



huzairulshazmey.vercel.app

WORK EXPERIENCES

JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER

Myaestic Sdn Bhd | 2021 - Present

- Assist with the creation of websites and update existing web applications using scripting languages
- Cooperate with web designers to match visual design intent.
- Illustrating design ideas using storyboards, process flows and sitemaps

SALE ASSISTANT

Elewsmart Sdn Bhd | February - April 2021

- Provide excellent customers service.
- Ensured the correct pricing, proper maintenance of rack labels, proper merchandising & storing of stocks.
- Maintained clean sales floor & straightened & faced merchandise.

SALE ASSISTANT

Parkson Holdings Berhad | November 2020 - January 2021

- Actively promote stocks, products information & promotional merchandise to customers.
- Help customers complete purchases & loacte items
- Restock, arranged & organized merchandise in front lanes to drive product sales

INDUSTRIAL TRAINING PROGRAM (INTERNSHIP)

Milkup Sdn Bhd

- Web administrators design, develop, maintain and troubleshoot websites. Most importantly, ensure a safe and efficient user experience.
- Editing photos and video related to company product.
- Build e-commerce websites using WordPress for company to start selling online.

EDUCATION

COLLEGE VOCATIONAL SEPANG 2015 - 2019

Diploma in Database and Web Application Malaysian Skills Certification

- Final year Project : develope website " ECadangan Dan Aduan Pelajar Kolej Vokasional Sepang"
- Developed E-commerce website using Wix, OpenCart and WordPress as a assingment.

SMK PUTRAJAYA PRESINT 18 (1)

SMK PUTRAJAYA PRESINT 18 (1) | 2013 - 2015